designerdigitals.com 2012-11-10

# DesignerDigitals Privacy Policy

## Dedicated to your privacy

Click Creative Group, Inc. is dedicated to maintaining and protecting your privacy. This includes the privacy of both your information and any and all orders placed with our website, DesignerDigitals.com. By using our website and products, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. This Policy explains what personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") we collect and how we use the information so we can continue to provide outstanding service and products to you.[](http://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.designerdigitals.com&sealid=101)

Click Creative Group, Inc. has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [_TRUSTe's program requirements_](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html "TRUSTe's program requirements") including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. This privacy statement covers the Web site DesignerDigitals.com.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Randy Pertiet at support@designerdigitals.com. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact TRUSTe [_here_](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint "TRUSTe").

Last Updated on March 29, 2011

* * *

## Information Collection and Use

 ** _Registration_**  
In order to use this Web site (DesignerDigitals.com), you must first complete the registration form and create a user name and password. In the store the user name will be your email address, while in the other areas of the site it will be a unique name that you create. During registration you are required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest as well as any CD (compact disk) orders that you order shipped directly to you.

Upon registration in the store or gallery, your email address will automatically be added to our weekly newsletter which contains site updates, events, sales and the like. If you wish to not receive the newsletter send us the request to **support@designerdigitals.com** or select the Un-Subscribe feature in the newsletter.

Click Creative Group, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on DesignerDigitals.com. Click Creative Group, Inc. collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at support@designerdigitals.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**_Testimonials_**  
We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information such as the customer's name. We review the content of the testimonials before the comments are available for public viewing to filter out any unwanted SPAM or profanity.

**_Orders_**  
If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).

We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

**_Surveys or Contests_**  
From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information such as name and shipping address.

We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes.

**_Email a Friend Feature_**  
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's mail address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit DesignerDigitals.com. Click Creative Group, Inc. does not store this information for further use.

**_Uses of Information_**  
The information collected is used in the processing of orders to verify correct ownership of the credit card used. We may use or disclose information about your demographics and use of the site in any manner that does not reveal your identity. E-mail addresses, postal addresses, or telephone numbers if provided may be used by us to communicate advance notice of events, new products and/or services, but is NOT sold to other sources. In addition, we do not retain your credit card information. Once an order is authorized, our server removes the card information. Demographic information is also used for target advertising by region only. 

## Communications from the Site

 ** _Special Offers and Updates_**  
We will occasionally send you information on sales and specials in the store.

Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see the "Choice and Opt-out."

**_Newsletters_**  
We will use your name and email address to send our weekly newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. Please see the "Choice and Opt-out" section.

**_Customer Service_**  
Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us we will communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone (if provided), in accordance with your wishes.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

 ** _Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)_**  
We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information nor do we share aggregate information.

 ** _Personally identifiable information_**  
We DO NOT Share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties except as outlined in this privacy policy.

**_Agents_**  
We use a credit card processing company ( **Authorize.net** ) to bill you for goods and services. This company does not share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purpose.

 ** _Service Providers_**  
We use Shutterfly to provide print services for the customers on our site. When you sign up with these services everything needed by them will be collected by Shutterfly in order to provide that service.

**_Legal Disclaimer_**  
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

**_Change in Ownership_**  
If DesignerDigitals.com is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

## Choice/Opt-out

We provide you the opportunity to "opt-out" of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate this by Un-Subscribing from our newsletters or announcements. You can also contact use at **support@designerdigitals.com** and we will remove your contact information per your request.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at **support@designerdigitals.com**.

We also provide you the ability to change and update the privacy settings of your profile. To do this log into your store account through the login box or by clicking on the link "My Account" on the upper right hand side of the store. Once there you can change or update your information under the links "Edit Account Info" and "My Address Book".

## Log Files

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

We use a third-party tracking service called Google Analytics that uses cookies and log files to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate. Google Analytics helps us find out what keywords attract desirable prospects, what advertising copy pulls the most responses, and what landing pages and content the customers are attracted to.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use session cookies to make store shopping cart information as well as shopping cart security. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. If you have not logged into or created an account in the store, any items in your shopping cart will be lost when you close your browser.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as our shopping cart, will be limited.

## Third Party Advertisers

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by our web server only and not a third party advertising site.

## Links to Other Sites

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled Click Creative Group, Inc. Please be aware that we, Click Creative Group, Inc., are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site.

## Forum/Gallery/Chat Rooms/WebLog (Blog)

We provide a forum, gallery and chat room on our site. You should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these areas.

We also provide a WebLog (Blog) on our site. This blog is internal to DesignerDigitals.com and does not allow comments from the general public. The purpose of the blog is to provide information about new events, contests and other such information that we deem relevant to interested parties. 

## Access to Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by by emailing our Customer Support at **support@designerdigitals.com** or by contacting us by postal mail at the contact information listed below.

To request the removal of an unauthorized account, please contact us at support@designerdigitals.com.

## Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card numbers) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). To learn more about SSL, follow this [_link_](http://www.verisign.com/ssl/ssl-information-center/extended-validation-ssl-certificates/index.html "SSL information").

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

DesignerDigitals.com and Click Creative Group, Inc. are also PCI DSS compliant. PCI DSS is an industry-wide security standard that is supported by the five major card brands including American Express, Discover Financial Services, JCB, MasterCard Worldwide, and Visa International providing numerous requirements for merchants and service providers surrounding the security for storing, transmitting, and processing cardholder data. To learn more about PCI DSS follow this [_link_](https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/ "PCI DSS").

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at **support@designerdigitals.com**.

## Business Transitions

In the event Click Creative Group, Inc. goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

## Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page prior to the changes taking effect.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: **support@designerdigitals.com** or by mail at:

 **Click Creative Group, Inc., 903 Cedarday Dr., Bel Air, MD 21015.**
